<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xjT-v7U8eE" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>Youtube Trending</title>
    <description>Listen to COMING HOME from the multi-platinum Grammy Award winning global entertainment icon here: https://ushermusic.lnk.to/COMINGHOME

“Risk It All” is a captivating track produced and written by H.E.R. and renowned songwriter Jimmy Napes. H.E.R.’s signature, compelling lyricism and impassioned production are put on display through velvety, soaring vocals that tug at the heartstrings. The song brings together these two award-winning superstars for a special collaboration that encapsulates the raw emotion and enduring strength of The Color Purple’s film’s narratives: risk, love and liberation. USHER’s signature smooth tones blend seamlessly with H.E.R.’s soulful depth, creating a hymn of resilience and courage. The “Risk It All” music video was directed by the award-winning master Dave Myers. 

USHER &amp; H.E.R. are joined on The Color Purple (Music From And Inspired By) Soundtrack by an incomparable array of music luminaries, including Alicia Keys, Megan Thee Stallion, Jennifer Hudson, Mary J. Blige, Fantasia, Missy Elliott, Halle Bailey, Keyshia Cole, Coco Jones, Taraji P. Henson, Timbaland, Jorja Smith, The-Dream, Celeste, Mary Mary, Darkchild, October London and more. The Color Purple (Music From And Inspired By) is the biggest R&amp;B soundtrack in decades, boasting 17 songs from the film, 16 newly penned songs and four remixes. The Color Purple Film is only in theaters starting December 25, 2023.

Listen to the Soundtrack: https://vydia.lnk.to/TheColorPurple

Follow USHER 
TikTok https://www.tiktok.com/@usher  
Instagram https://www.instagram.com/usher  
Twitter https://twitter.com/usher
Facebook https://www.facebook.com/usher
Youtube https://www.youtube.com/usher

Lyrics:
Like a condition, like a religion 
So easily mistreated
Scary decision 
Sometimes it’s hell and sometimes it’s heaven 
It’s overcomplicated, but baby, I don’t mind 

Feeling like I’m bound to fall
Close my eyes 
Baby, I would risk it all, yeah 

Sometimes it’s tragic, so problematic 
People are crying for it 
People are dying for it 
Always the reason we still believe in 
Something that leaves us hurting
It’s worth it, I don’t mind 

Feeling like I’m bound to fall
Close my eyes 
Baby, I would risk it all 
Just to be in love 
I just wanna be in love 
Be in love 

I don’t mind 
Feeling like I’m bound to fall
Baby, I close my eyes
Baby, I would risk it all 
I don’t mind 
Feeling like I’m bound to fall
Close my eyes 
Baby, I would risk it all 
Oh, just to be in love 
Be in love

Music Video Credits:
directed by dave meyers

production company: freenjoy
director rep: lark creative
produced by nathan scherrer, stephan bielecki &amp; brian bell
director of photography: scott cunningham
choreographer: tessandra chavez
editor: nathan rodgers
color: pavel marko
vfx supervisor: jan malíř
vfx by UPP

dancers: 
kerrynton alyssa jones
jada e'vai walker
tash crudup
briana bri morrison
jarrett mackenzie
leconte banks
jovanni soto
byron patrick tittle
brandon o'neal
denzel chisolm

#USHER #HER #RiskItAll #TheColorPurple

http://vevo.ly/4ohcoC</description>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com</link>
    <generator>json2rss</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>

